njschooljobs.com 2019-12-25

# NJSchoolJobs | Education

### Our Commitment to Privacy

To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, it is available on our homepage and wherever personally identifiable information may be requested. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on our website.

### The Information We Collect

When you browse our website, your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) is recorded so that we may know how you are using our website. Your browser may also automatically provide us with information regarding your computer and operating system. This information is used by us to monitor and improve our website. This information is not linked back to you as an individual user.

The purpose of our website is to allow you to broadcast information about yourself to gain employment. You may apply to jobs on the website where your information will be sent to the employer listing the job opening. You may also choose whether to be searchable by employers looking to fill positions through our resume search feature.

We collect some or all of the following information when you register as a job seeker:

  * Contact information including, but not limited to, name, email address, phone numbers, and street address.
  * Your resume including, but not limited to, work experience, education, and other history. Some employers may ask for demographics including race, ethnicity, and gender. This is always optional.
  * Any information you use to apply to jobs on our website including, but not limited to, employer generated screening questions.
  * Activity history including, but not limited to, applications submitted, searches, and jobs clicked on.

We collect some or all of the following information when you register as an employer:

  * Contact information including, but not limited to, name, email address, phone numbers, and street address.
  * Business information including, but not limited to, name, type, and size.
  * Purchasing history.
  * Billing information for services requiring payments.
  * Activity history including, but not limited to, jobs, applicants, resume searches, notes, forwarded applications and resumes, and messages.

If you use our referral feature (Tell-a-friend) to let a friend know about a job or the website, we store the email address and name of the person to whom you sent the message.

### The Way We Use Information

We use collected information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. Your personal information may be used for:

  * Connecting job seekers with employers looking to hire.
  * Maintaining a job seeker account including resumes you may upload or create.
  * Enabling you to search for and apply to jobs and share them with others.
  * Allowing employers to find your resume if you desire and contact you.
  * Allowing us to contact you about relevant job openings and other career related information through the use of job alerts and other messages.
  * Monitoring and investigating activities that may be fraudulent or deceptive.

### How We Share Information

We share the information that we collect from you with our affiliated companies, recruiters, and service providers. Recruiters may use your information to contact you directly. Additionally, when you apply for a job with an employer, the information you supply or share through our website may become part of that employer’s database. If your profile is accessed by an employer, your information may become a part of their database. In these instances, the use of such information by the recruiter will be subject to the privacy policy of that company, and we are not responsible for that company’s use of your information.

By applying to a job, providing your contact information to show interest in a job, or replying to a message from an employer, you consent to the disclosure of your information and communication with that employer for employment related purposes.

We attempt to limit access to our resume database to legitimate employers but we cannot guarantee that other parties will not gain access to this database for fraudulent purposes. Accordingly, you should use caution when storing sensitive information you would not want made public.

We may also share your information with third parties who provide specific technical services to aid the operation of the website including website hosting, credit card processing, and SMS and email messaging.

### Cookie Policy

We and our technical partners use cookies (small text files on your computer or mobile device) to operate the website and services.

  * Essential cookies – these are important to make the website function properly. They are not involved in tracking.
  * Performance cookies – these include Google analytics cookies to collect information about behavior so we can continually enhance the user experience.
  * Third-party cookies – Some of our webpages use third-party services or software, such as maps, online videos or social networking features. Many of these services may set cookies on your device.
  * Advertising cookies – we may use tracking cookies to assist with delivering online ads.

### How You Can Correct Your Information

At any time, you may obtain a summary of your personal information on record with us. You may also request that we dispose of any or all personal information about you, except for personal information we need to complete transactions or to maintain proper records of previous transactions. You can help us maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying us of any change to your personal information.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, or our handling of your personal information, please contact us via our contact page. We welcome comments and suggestions concerning this Privacy Policy. We are committed to respecting your privacy and protecting your personal information.

### Your Acceptance of These Terms

By using our website, you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any revisions will be posted on this site. Please check this page periodically for changes.
